<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Better Vanilla" Logo="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/883154737439072316/981346715871367208/logo.png" Description="">
		<Server Name="Better Vanilla Normal Version" Logo="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/883154737439072316/981346715871367208/logo.png">
			<Description>

A20 (Final) update for the Better Vanilla. (from 22.01.2023)
- Attention, This is the Better Vanilla normal version. Here all zombies have the boosted HP
- Attention! Easy Anti Cheat (EAC) must be disabled.

This is the Better Vanilla Overhaul mod. This mod was made how I like to play 7 Days to Die.
Since there were a lot of requests, I published the Better Vanilla.

You can read about everything that has changed in my Discord in the Better Vanilla area.
There are also other downloads in the Discord such as:
- Better Vanilla Walking Dead Version
- a zombie navigation
- the Better Vanilla ComboPack 48.1 + pre-made CP maps

I will also help with problems, questions and suggestions as best I can. 
And the existing community is also very happy to help!

Discord: https://discord.gg/qdwbN9VW87 

Have fun in the Better Vanilla!
Best Regards, 
Saxe82

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

A20 (Final) update für die Better Vanilla. (22.01.2023)
- Achtung, Dies ist die Better Vanilla Normal-Version. Hier haben alle Zombies die angehobene HP.			
- Achtung! Easy Anti Cheat (EAC) muss deaktiviert sein.

Dies ist die Better Vanilla Overhaul Mod. Diese Mod ist so erstellt wurden, wie ich gerne 7 Days to Die spiele. 
Da sehr viele Anfragen kamen, habe ich die Better Vanilla veröffentlicht.

Was alles Verändert wurde, könnt ihr in meinem Discord im Bereich Better Vanilla nachlesen.
Im Discord gibt es außerdem weitere Download wie:
- Better Vanilla Walking Dead Version
- eine Zombie Navigation
- das Better Vanilla ComboPack 48.1 + vorgefertigste CP-Maps

Auch werde ich bei Problemen, Fragen und Anregungen zur Seite stehen, so gut ich kann. 
Und die vorhandene Community hilft auch sehr gern!				

Discord: https://discord.gg/qdwbN9VW87 

Viel Spaß in der Better Vanilla!
Mit freundlichen Grüßen, 
Saxe82

			</Description>
				<Downloads>
					<Download>https://dev.azure.com/saxe1982/BetterVanilla/_git/BetterVanilla</Download>
				</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
